Priya Yadav

Profile- Experienced Professional in IT, Internet, E-commerce, and media industry with in depth knowledge of related practices and market fluctuations. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction, Project management, proven record of outperforming project objectives, exceeding service standards. Enthusiastic about using skills to boost and support the company objectives and success.

Employment History

Consultant-Bombinate Technologies Private Limited, Bangalore, India. Feb, 2019 - Sep, 2020.

KOO & VOKAL APP

- Liaised with users, C-Level Executive and product development team to convey the product (App) feature requests, and product (app)development suggestion.
- Worked on improving customer satisfaction and app ratings by resolving issues, monitoring product (App) performance on the Google Play Console and tracking requirements and bugs related to the product and worked closely with the engineering team.
- Drafted product design throughout results in end to end process improvement.
- Conduct day-to-day project coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams.
- Worked to establish and implement strategic plans designed to capitalize on ongoing opportunities and achieve growth.
- Align goals with top management on project scheduling budgeting, resource management in order to keep company growth at its best.

Consultant - India Today Group, Noida, India. JUNE, 2017 - NOV, 2017.

- Developed campaigns, specific marketing strategies, media planning, and presentations.
- Conduct promotional activities and takes part in strategies discussions and implementation.
- Recorded data in Excel databases, streamlining analysis procedures for efficiency and accuracy.
- Monitoring and Evaluating KPIs for business growth.



BGM-Weidemaier Str. 6, Leimen,69181, Germany yadu20priya@gmail.com +49 015739036150

Skills

- JIRA ,Asana
- MS Office
- Google Suite
- Google Analytics

D.O.B - 12th Aug, 1993

- Google Ads
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Tailwind
- Risk Management
- Time Management
- Tracking and Monitoring
- Business Development
- Digital Marketing
- Project Planning

Language

- English (Fluent)
- German (Business Proficiency)
- Hindi (Native)

Counsellor - Live Kampuzz Pvt Ltd. Noida, India. MARCH, 2016 - MAY, 2017.

- Maintained relationships with the university. Gathered necessary paperwork and applications for international and national students to initiate the enrollment process.
- Counseled students regarding educational issues such as course and program selection, class scheduling and registration, and career planning and selecting courses to align with interests and abilities.
 Organized college tours for students and their parents.

Business Developer - iProf E-Learning Solutions Pvt Ltd. Noida, India.

JULY, 2014 - FEB, 2016.

- Increased sales by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.
- Communicated with customers to understand needs and recommend appropriate solutions.

Education

MBA -Dr. A.P.J Abdul Kalam University, Lucknow, U.P India - 2012 - 2014.

BBA - VBSP University, Jaunpur, U.P, India - 2009 - 2012.

10+2 (PCM), U.P, India - 2009.

German Language Course(B1), VHS, Germany - JUNE, 2021 - OCT, 2021.

German Language Course(B2- Professional), VHS, Germany - Jan, 2022 - July, 2022.

Web and App Development- WBS Coding School, Berlin, Germany - Jan, 2023- May, 2023.

Certificaions

- Google Analytics.
- Google Ads Display Certification.
- Excel for Business Analysts.
- Telc German B1

Dissertation

 Increasing Role of Digital Media in Promotion of Brands.

Research Report

 Customer preference towards Parag Dairy.